m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译 草草
翻译 Somehacker
翻译 天意 Silmar
翻译 阿蘅 李SIR
时间轴 Imok
时间轴 aaa
后期  铭哥骑白马
校对&总监 天意
大西洋
帝国
『第四季 第五集』
前情提要
你想让我假扮你妻子
You want me to pretend to be your wife?
作为绅士  是不该问女士这种问题的
That's not something a gentleman would ask of a lady.
根本不用问
You didn't even have to.
会有人来跟你攀谈
A man will approach you.
有给布朗先生的包裹吗
You got a package for Mr. Brown?
把钱给他  只能给他
Give him the cash and only him.
老伙计亨利  我的好朋友
My old pal Henry. My buddy.
镁乳怎么样
How about milk of magnesia?
我们在课上分解它的时候
When we broke it down in class,
光是闻着气味就呛出眼泪了
I got the squirts just smelling it.
想法不错  林肯
I like your thinkin', Lincoln.
各位
Hey, everyone.
亨利再给我们来一个查尔斯顿舞怎么样
Who thinks Henry should show us the Charleston again?
可是我的孙子应当在我身旁
My grandson belongs with me.
他该回家了
It's time he came home.
你知道这是什么吗
Do you know what this is?
海洛因
Heroin.
你可以给我卖力
You could work for me.
选举就要开始了
Election's coming up.
我们会赢的
We get that sewed up,
事情也会随之越来越多
things are bound to get busier.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
I'm fine, yes.
有家人吗
Got a family?
两个儿子
Ah, two sons.
他们都长大了
Both of them grown.
敬新人生  卡彭先生
To new lives, Mr. Capone.
威利  醒醒
Willie, wake up.
他整晚都在去厕所  我听到了
He kept going to the bathroom all night. I heard him.
-凯斯勒先生  -什么事
- Mr. Kessler. - Yes?
我们是调查局的人
We're with the Bureau of Investigation.
但是我没做什么
But I have done--
乖乖跟我们走
One foot in front of the other.
喂
Hello?
-努基叔叔  -威利
- Uncle Nucky. - Willie?
你好吗
How are you?
你从哪打来的
Where are you calling from?
费城
Philadelphia.
我在费城
I'm in Philadelphia and...
威利  出什么事了
Willie, is something wrong?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
埃迪
Eddie!
埃迪  你在吗
Eddie, are you up there?
埃迪
Eddie.
Eddie?
汤普森先生
Mr. Thompson.
-你今天见到他了吗  -没有
- Have you seen him today? - No.
把车开过来  快点
Bring the car around. Make it quick.
要来点吗
Would you like some?
你可以接受或拒绝
You can say yes or no.
我们不会为此强迫你什么
Doesn't obligate you to anything.
不了  谢谢
No, thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
这么说感觉怪怪的
Sounds funny, doesn't it?
-怎么  -他说  "不了  谢谢"
- How's that? - He said, "No, thank you."
我说"不客气"  感觉怪怪的
I said, "You're welcome." Doesn't sound right.
你觉得呢
Sound right to you?
我对你说"不了  谢谢"
You do not say "You're welcome"
你不该回答"不客气"
when someone says "No, thank you."
为什么
Why?
因为他们没有接受你的任何东西
Because they have not accepted anything from you.
他的英语比你还好呢
His English is better than yours.
可不是嘛
Heck, I guess it is.
你去哪学的
Where did you learn it?
你是在普鲁士学的吗
Did you study it over in Prussia,
你是这么叫的吧
I guess you would have called it?
为什么带我来这儿
Why am I here?
-你说呢  -我不知道
- Why do you think you're here? - I do not know.
人们不会无缘无故被人从大街上带走
People don't get hauled off the street for no reason, do they?
人们会无缘无故被从大街上带走吗
Do they get hauled off the street for no reason?
我不是警察
I am not a policeman.
-没人认为你是警察  -我们才是警察
- No one thinks you're a policeman. - We're the policemen.
我什么都没做
I have done nothing wrong.
你袖子里有把枪
You had a pistol up your sleeve.
-那是防身用  -防着谁
- That is for protection. - Against who?
阿帕奇人[北美原住民]
Apaches.
你说我们该怎么做
What do you think we should do?
看来是没别的办法了
Don't see what choice we have.
该死的  真他妈该死
Darn it. Darn it to heck.
嗯
Yeah.
我可以走了吗
I may leave?
-你差点摔倒了  -我没事
- You almost fell. - I am fine.
我觉得你有事
You don't look fine.
你看起来很不稳当
You look very unsteady.
我觉得你该在这儿多待一会儿
I think you should stay here for a while.
这是为了你好
For your own good.
给比尔·弗拉姆一把扫帚
Give Bill Pflaum the broom
他会扫净西塞罗
and he'll sweep Cicero clean.
支持比尔
Stand beside Bill,
他会为你们挺身而出
and he'll stand up for you.
干净的城市才能欣欣向荣
A straight town is a healthy town.
对你  对你的家人都好
Healthy for your family and healthy for you.
让我们握手言欢
So let's shake hands...
为什么他们要一大早扰人清梦
Why must they disturb the people so early?
今天是选举日
It's Election Day, dear.
他们有权进行宣传
They have the right to campaign.
他们不该这么大吵大闹
They should not make so much fuss
并且老实听命
and do what they are told.
那可不民主
That wouldn't be very democratic.
说话人人都会
Everybody is talking always.
观点人人都有
Everybody has the opinion.
-可什么事都干不成  -爸爸
- Nothing gets done. - Dada.
-他得吃东西  -他不想再吃了
- He must eat. - He doesn't want any more.
他还不知道自己想要什么
He does not know what he wants.
你的朋友又来了
Your friends have returned.
这都是你自己建的吗
Built this whole thing yourself?
用的罗塞塔模型
The Rosetta model.
种点草  装点一下
Put some grass down there. Spruce it up.
那是夏季的活儿了
That's the summer project.
该上早班了
Time for the morning shift.
走吧  乔治
Let's go, George.
今天是个好日子
Gonna be a good day.
你还好吗  威尔
How are you, Will?
我挺好
I'm okay.
受惊了吧
A little shaken?
没有  我...
No, I'm--
是啊
yeah.
我们会解决这事的
We'll sort this out.
这你要明白
That's the first thing you need to know.
我爸妈
Do my parents--
现在  这事就是你知我知
Right now this is between us.
我会尽力保持这个局面
I'm gonna do my best to keep it that way.
他们还没提出起诉  这是好事
They haven't chargedouou yet. That's very good.
我为什么不能走
Why can't I leave?
有些记者赖在楼上大堂不走
There are reporters upstairs living in the lobby
就摩拳擦掌地等着呢
just looking for something to do.
你可以以大案嫌疑人的身份从这儿走出去
You can walk out of here a suspect in a capital case.
他们瞬间就能感觉出来
They'll smell that in a second.
或者你也可以像付罚单的人一样走出去
Or you can walk out like someone who just paid a parking ticket.
这是我们要的效果
That's what we want.
你得给我点时间
You need to give me a little time.
但是
But you--
你在费城认识人吧
you know people in Philadelphia, right?
是认识  我会去找他们的
I do and I'll call on them.
如果有这必要的话
If that's what's required.
我会补偿你的  我保证
I'll make it up to you. I swear.
现在先别去想那些
Don't worry about that now.
我们先谈谈那个男孩
Let's talk about this boy.
我跟那事毫无关系
I didn't have anything to do with it.
我们先谈谈他  就一会儿
Let's just talk about him for a minute.
好了
Now, now.
阿灵顿饭店
Hotel Arlington.
请接罗伊·菲利普斯先生
Yes, Mr. Roy Phillips, please.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
我认为这与你无关吧
I don't see how that's any of your concern.
我怎么知道他还没到...
How do I know he hasn't arrived since the last time I--
是的  相同的留言
Yes. The same message.
没事
It's all right.
-老大  -给我们让路
- Hey, boss. - Clear a path, boys.
-早啊  弗兰克  -早
- Hey, Frank. - Morning.
-老大  一切还好啊  -弗兰克
- How's it going, boss? - Frank.
我听说弗拉姆昨晚上挨打了
So I heard Pflaum caught a couple last night.
不  他们只是打碎了他的膝盖
No, they just capped his knees.
这事我可不知道
I don't know nothing about that.
那在二十二街被人割喉的家伙呢
What about the guy that got his throat cut on 22nd?
喉咙完全割开了吗
His whole throat?
没有  只到这儿
Nah, only to here.
那他还能吹箫喽
So he can still whistle, huh?
说得好  弗兰克
That's a good one, Frank.
去看看殿下吧
Let's check in on His Highness.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
跳蚤杂技表演训练  你说呢
Training my flea circus. What do you think?
还是放一放吧
Why don't you give it a break?
怎么  好像你自己没吸过一样
What, like you ain't been touching it?
今天有正事
We got business today.
我刚说什么了
What'd I just say?
别这样
Don't do that.
怎么  以为我开玩笑呢
What, you think I'm kidding?
把那玩意收起来
Put that thing away.
他他妈来干什么
What the fuck's he doing here?
是你自己要见他
You asked for him, Garibaldi.
你喜欢他昨晚的处事方式
You liked the way he handled himself last night.
是吗
I did?
林子里的事
The woods!
丹尼尔·克罗克特
Daniel fucking Crockett.
"你还是逃命去吧"
"You'd better run."
乔治  知道今天是什么日子吗
Hey, George, you know what day it is?
-竞选日  -愚人节
- Election Day. - April Fools'.
那些蠢货  会发现自己现了洋相
All the suckers, they're gonna find out that the joke's on them.
知道我说的是谁吗
You know who that includes?
-不知道  -你猜
- I don't. - Guess.
-猜不出  -这个人喜欢花
- I can't. - He likes flowers.
奥巴尼恩先生
Mr. O'Banion.
你听听
Listen to him.
过来
Come here.
再近些
Closer.
来啊
Come on.
我不会打你的
I won't hurt you.
你做过坏事
You done bad things.
我看到了
I saw you.
你也一样
So have you.
对  我做过  但不是对自己老板
Yes, I have. But not to the guy I work for.
你有点儿野性难驯啊
You got a little wild streak.
是不是
Huh?
看看你今天的表现
Let's see how you do today.
然后我们再谈
Then we'll talk.
因为我们和卖花的还有账要算
'Cause there's some unfinished business with the florist.
回头再说
Leave all that for later.
阿尔
Al.
出去找二十个你最棒的人手
Go out there, pick the 20 best men you can find,
带他们去西电公司大门
take them over to the main gate at Western Electric.
帮选民定下主意
Help the voters make up their minds.
你一起来吗
You with us?
他得问他老婆
He needs to ask his wife.
我不需要问任何人
I don't need to ask anyone anything.
我看他是想咬我了
I think he wants to bite me.
别太过分
Respect the boundaries, huh?
家伙还在吗
Still got that piece?
这个吗
You mean this?
收好
Hold on.
应该用不上  不过...
Shouldn't be any need, but...
你可以吧
Are you okay, then?
来精神精神
Perk yourself up.
我现在就很好
I'm fine right now.
不想做我朋友吗
Don't you want to be my friend?
谁敢跟我们作对
Yeah! Who's gonna fuck with us, huh?
我们开了个派对
We had a party.
你们是谁
Who's we?
就是几个朋友
Just the fellas,
我和舍友克莱顿
my roommate Clayton and me.
几个女孩
Some girls.
派对上有酒
There was liquor.
哪儿来的
Where'd that come from?
威利  你得告诉我
Will, you need to tell me.
酒是...
It was...
多伊尔先生
Mr. Doyle.
米奇卖你酒
Mickey sold you liquor?
为什么不找我
Why didn't you come to me?
我不想让你知道
I didn't want you to know.
可我现在知道了
But I know now.
懂了吗  威利
You see, Will?
酒是我的酒
The liquor came from me.
而我不知情  现在就有了问题
I didn't know, and now there's a problem.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我是个白痴  非常抱歉
I'm an idiot. I'm sorry.
好吧  米奇卖给你酒
All right, Mickey sold you liquor.
你带回学校
You brought it back to school.
只是个派对
It was just a party.
大家都玩得很开心
everybody was having a good time.
第二天早上亨利就
The next morning Henry was
就不动了
he wasn't moving.
我不知道
I don't know.
他喝的多吗
Did he drink a lot?
跟其他人差不多
As much as anyone else.
-可他是唯一一个...  -是的
- But he was the only one who-- - Yes.
你和他有多熟悉
How well d did you know him?
不熟悉
I didn't.
我以为他是你朋友
I thought he was your friend.
什么
What?
我们吃饭的时候  你管他叫朋友
When we had dinner, you called him a friend.
我在这里没有多少朋友  努基伯父
I don't have a lot of friends here, Uncle Nucky.
我要去跟地方检察官谈谈
I'm going to talk to the district attorney.
如果他只是试探  我会知道
If he's just fishing, then I'll know it
然后一切都会过去
and it all goes away.
你要做的是  振作起来
What you have to do is pull yourself together
记住事实真相
and remember the truth.
我再问你一次
Let me ask you again,
亨利是你的朋友吗
was Henry your friend?
是的
Yes.
他喝了多少
How much did he drink?
很多
A lot.
你从哪弄的酒
Where did you get the liquor?
我没带酒
I didn't bring any liquor.
很好
Good.
在对您的住所进行检查之后
Following an inspection of your domicile,
警察会提供一份报告...
the officer will submit a report--
达莫迪夫人
Mrs. Darmody?
达莫迪夫人  您没事吧
Mrs. Darmody, are you all right?
您看起来有些憔悴
You're looking a bit peaked.
我昨晚一夜没睡
I didn't sleep last night.
我替您难过
I'm sorry to hear it.
我忽然醒来  想到
I wake up and I think,
"我得去看看汤米"
"Must check on Tommy."
-起床之后才想起...  -是啊
- I'm out of bed and I realize-- - Yes.
才想起他不在家里
I realize he's not there.
然后就睡不着
And there's no getting back to sleep.
一直无法入睡
Not at all.
警官的报告呈上来后
After the officer submits a report,
法院会对抚养权一事
the court will make its final determination
做出最终判决
regarding the question of custody.
我需要做些什么
What do I have to do?
您不需要做任何事情
You don't have to do anything.
警官要看到的是男孩将回到的那个家
What the officer will be looking for is a true picture
最真实的模样
of the home the boy would be returning to.
我正在做一些改动
I'm in a period of transition.
很多家具...
A great deal of the furniture--
家具并不重要
The furniture is not important.
我最近在交往的一位绅士
A gentleman I've been seeing,
是一家重要国家公司的高管
he's highly placed in an important national firm.
责任重大
A great deal of responsibility.
他不想遭人议论
He'd prefer not to have that bandied about.
他以谨慎为荣
He prides himself on discretion.
还有他对装饰的品味
And his taste in decor is...
我能麻烦您倒杯水吗
May I trouble you for a glass of water?
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-没关系  -我不知道我今天是怎么了
- It's all right. - I don't know what's wrong with me today.
天呐
Oh, dear.
拿着
Here.
攥紧一会儿
Clench it tight for a minute.
我看起来一定很糟糕
I must look quite a horror.
一点也不
Not at all.
我今天很不在状态
I'm just in such a state.
你到达了一个人生的阶段
You reach a point in life and you
意识到自己撇下的才是最重要的
realize it's what you leave behind that matters.
汤米可能一点都不记得我
And the thought that Tommy might not remember me at all,
就好像我从未存在过
as if I never even existed.
最好一步一步来
Best to take it one step at a time.
我可以做些什么来改变我的状况吗
Is there anything I can do to help my situation?
-我解释过  -我说现在
- As I explained-- - I mean right now.
现在我能做什么吗
Is there anything I can do right now?
-达莫迪夫人  -什么事
- Mrs. Darmody. - Yes?
你最好马上离开
It would be in your best interest
这间办公室
to leave these chambers immediately.
我有约会要迟到了
I'm late for an appointment.
汤普森先生  我是尤金·莫赫恩
Mr. Thompson. Eugene Mulhearne.
助理地方检察官  你好
I'm an assistant district attorney. How do you do?
莫赫恩先生  我要见的不是你
Mr. Mulhearne, you're not who I want to see.
地方检察官让我来见你
The district attorney asked me to meet with you
回答你所问的问题
and answer any questions you might have.
-他为什么不在这  -很遗憾他有要事在身
- Why isn't he here? - He had other obligations, regretfully.
-你们犯错了  -此话怎讲
- You fellows are making a mistake. - How's that?
要把一个的不幸的事件变成什么
Trying to turn a quirk of fate into what?
谋杀案
A manslaughter charge?
十个目击者说他把酒带到了那个派对上
10 separate witnesses say he brought liquor to that party.
这件事值得你浪费时间和精力吗
Is that really worth your time and effort?
如果那个男孩是被毒死的  那就值得
If that boy was poisoned, then yes.
你从哪里得到那个信息的
Where are you getting that from?
他的症状与中毒相符合
His symptoms are consistent with poisoning.
-酒精中毒  -验尸官可不是这么说的
- Alcohol poisoning. - That's not what the coroner says.
跟我侄子有什么关系
What's that got to do with my nephew?
警局会查出来的
This office intends to find out.
我们别说废话  你的老板和瓦克西·戈登
Let's cut the bullshit. Your boss and Waxey Gordon
今早应我邀请进行了一次谈话
had a conversation this morning at my request
并达成共识  这个事件尽管很让人痛心
and it was agreed that this occurrence,
但不是任何人的过失
terrible as it was, isn't anybody's fault.
外面的那对夫妇
That couple outside,
是亨利·盖恩斯的父母
they're Henry Gaines's parents.
盖恩斯先生是宾州共和党的
Mr. Gaines is a major contributor
一位重要捐款人
to the Pennsylvania Republican Party.
他痛失爱子
He's lost his son
他可不想听到这是什么人生的不幸
and he doesn't want to hear about life's random misfortunes.
肯定要有人承担
Someone's got to answer for this.
我们没有办法
We just don't have any choice.
-你怎么样了  -我很好
- How are we keeping? - I am fine.
你很好
You are fine.
我欣赏你的骨气
I admire that kind of backbone.
他知道你有多坚强吗
Does he know how tough you are?
谁
Who?
你的老板  汤普森先生
Your boss, Mr. Thompson.
我明白  好士兵
I understand. Good soldier.
说真的  我越来越喜欢你了
Really, the more I see of you, the more I like.
但是我要问问你
But let me ask this--
他也会为你做这样的事吗
would he do the same for you?
你在这一整天了  埃迪
You've been here all day, Eddie.
没有人找你
No one's asked for you.
木板路上  玛瑙俱乐部没有人找你
Not on the boardwalk, not over at the Onyx Club,
没人打电话  没人发电报
not in the speaks or the wire rooms.
世界抛弃了你
The world is going on without you.
努基·汤普森抛弃了你
Nucky Thompson is going on without you.
此时此刻
And the only person who
唯一一个关心你的人
really cares what happens to you right now
就是我
is me.
你是我的朋友吗
You are my friend?
我不是
No, I am not.
那你是谁
Then who are you?
这就是我
That's who I am.
我要折磨你到死
And I'm going to own every last bit of you.
把自己收拾干净
Clean yourself up.
谁是亨利·盖恩斯
Who was Henry Gaines?
是我的一位朋友
He was a friend of mine.
酒是谁带来的
Who brought the liquor?
不清楚
Beats me.
亨利喝了多少
How much did Henry drink?
很多
A lot.
谁给的他毒酒
Who slipped him the Mickey?
什么
The what?
混了毒药的酒  让他致死的那杯酒
The Mickey Finn. The knockout punch.
里面有什么东西
Whatever was in there.
我  我不知道
I-- I don't, uh--
威利  你不要跟我撒谎
Willie, I have to ask you not to lie just now.
没好处  坦白讲  我也不喜欢
It won't help. And frankly, I don't like it.
我需要知道真相
I need to know what's true
这样我们就能统一口径  明白吗
so we can agree on the rest. Understood?
只是个恶作剧而已
It was supposed to be a gag.
就这样
That's all.
主意是谁出的
Whose idea was it?
我
Mine.
就你自己
Just yours?
威利
Willie.
克莱顿帮我了
Clayton helped me.
你的室友
Your roommate?
亨利呢
And Henry?
他做了什么落到这个下场
What did he do to deserve it?
他觉得他比我强
He thought he was better than me.
但是他没有
But he wasn't.
好吧
All right.
我需要你这么做
Here's what I'm going to need you to do.
工厂的门在那
Factory gates are there,
投票站在那边
polling booth down that way.
你知道该怎么做
You know the situation.
确保他们投票给科林哈
Make sure they vote for Klenha
要不然就不许投
or don't vote at all.
大多数人  不想找麻烦
Most people, they don't want trouble.
谁当市长  谁当总统
Who's the mayor, who's the president,
对他们来说算什么
what's it to them?
我们来管理这个镇
We'll run this burg.
保持财源滚滚
Keep the green flowing.
这才是大家所在乎的
That's all anyone cares about.
奥巴尼恩呢
And O'Banion?
做事的方法有很多种
Lots of ways to do business.
看看进展如何吧
See how it plays out.
家伙带了吗
Got the piece?
在这里
Right here.
那就行动吧
Then hop to it.
不用担心我弟弟  好吗
Don't worry about my brother, okay?
有时他需要被教训一番
Sometimes he just needs a good kick in the ass.
谁来教训他
Who's gonna do the kicking?
这是预付
It's an advance.
跟着我
Stick with me, huh?
我给你的院子铺草
I'll put grass on your fucking lawn.
西电公司
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你好
Hello.
一切皆在掌控之中
There's no reason for this to get out of hand.
我们要做的就是提醒他们
All we need to do is remind them
投给共和党
why it's in their own
是最明智之举
best interest to elect the Republican ticket.
一有工人过来  你们就询问
As each worker goes by, I want you to inquire
-他要投给谁  -询问
- how he intends to vote. - Inquire?
他们清楚自己的举动所带来的后果
They already know what can happen
大多数人都不想惹上麻烦
and most people don't want trouble.
我可不是来和平谈判的
I didn't come out for no tea social.
-阿尔说给他们点颜色瞧瞧  -阿尔不管这里
- Al says give it to 'em good. - Al's not in charge here.
-我管  -你管个屁啊
- I am. - You ain't in charge of nothing.
我们把第一个走出来的人狠揍一顿
I say we pick the first guy and clobber him.
-按我说的做  -不然呢
- We're doing it my way. - Or what?
你动手试试
Go ahead and try.
-让一让  -让一让
- Coming through. - Coming through here.
-你投给谁了  -关你屁事儿
- Who you voting for today? - None of your damn business.
-投给共和党  朋友  -与你何干
- Voting Republican, friend? - What's it to you?
有空吗
Got a minute?
等一下
Hold on there.
我在和你说话
I'm talking to you.
站住  天杀的
Just stop for a second, God damn it!
回去  回去
Move back! Move back!
走  乔尼  快走  快走
Come on. Johnny, go, go! Let's go, let's go!
瞧  这些都不必发生的
You see, none of this had to happen.
快快  让我进去  让我进去
Move, move! Let me in! Let me in!
进去
Get inside!
我...
I, uh...
想找个人
I'm looking for someone.
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name,
但有人告诉我能在这里找到他
but I'm told he could be found here.
我知道我们以前从未见过
I realize we've never met before.
可能你一般不这么做生意
This is probably not how you normally conduct business,
不过我问过别人
but I made some inquires.
所以我来了
Here I am.
你离家太远了  牧羊女
You far from home, Bo Peep.
出自美国童谣《小牧羊女》
这里事事都是有关联的
Nothing is very far from anything here.
对吧
Is it?
皮都快被你擦掉了
You're gonna take the skin off.
谁告诉你来这儿的
Who sent you around?
很重要吗
Does that matter?
我得知道我的顾客从哪里来的
I like to know where my customers come from.
我吃过几年舞台饭
I spent several years on the stage.
继续说
Do tell.
-你知道混演艺圈的人是怎么样的  -怎么样
- You know how show people are. - How are they?
我们都喜欢把耳朵贴着地板
We like to keep our ears close to the ground.
你攥着的手袋里有多少呢
Well, what you got tucked up your little pouch there?
我能先看看货吗
May I examine the preparation first?
恐怕不行
No, you mayn't.
我只有这么多
That's all I've got.
那你还是去别处吧
Then you find that lost sheep somewhere else.
我能用其他的东西付款吗
Perhaps we could discuss another form of payment?
我日子不太好过  您贵姓
I'm having a difficult day, Mr...?
-牛津  -牛津先生
- Oxford. - Mr. Oxford.
很艰难的日子
A very difficult day.
某些时候
Just one of those times
需要一些小小的帮助
when you need a little extra help.
仅此而已
That's all this is.
你最好悠着点  小牧羊女
You best go easy now, Little Bo.
我希望我的小羊知道回家
I like my lambs keep coming home.
我去了哪里
Where I went?
特伦顿的师范学校
State Normal over in Trenton.
你阿姨梅布尔也在那里
Your Aunt Mabel was there.
她想做一名教师
She was going to be a teacher.
我不喜欢别的人
I didn't like the idea of other fellas
帮助她的课业
helping her with the classwork.
所以  我也决定做一名教师
So I thought I'd be a teacher, too.
为什么没做成
Why didn't you?
准将需要我
The Commodore needed me.
所以我回来了
And I came back home.
比起个人娱乐之事
There are more important things than what may
还有更重要的事等着你
or may not have happened at some party.
我爸爸不会知道
My father won't know?
没人会知道
No one will know.
汤普森先生  我是劳伦斯·埃斯利
Mr. Thompson. Lawrence Eisley.
检察官先生
Mr. District Attorney.
谢谢抽时间来
Thanks for making the time.
-之前的事情很抱歉  -没关系
- Sorry for the mix-up earlier. - Not to worry.
不过你肯定能理解我的担心
But I'm sure you can appreciate my concern.
如果是我侄子  我肯定和你一样的反应
Oh, I'd feel the same way if it was my nephew.
趁事情闹大之前  我们得弄清楚
We want to get this cleared up before it turns into something.
完全理解
I completely understand.
年轻人
Well, young man,
有人说你能
I'm told you might be able to help us
帮助我们调查这件不幸之事
with this unfortunate event.
你记得什么就告诉他们
You just tell them what happened as best you remember it.
首先  我要说...
First thing I want to say is...
亨利·盖恩斯是我的朋友
Henry Gaines was a pal of mine.
别跑
No running.
你们都是绅士和淑女
We are ladies and gentlemen here.
汤米  我给你说过无数次了  慢慢走
Tommy, I've told you time and time again, walking.
亲爱的
Darling.
是我啊  我是奶奶
It's me. It's Mima.
瞧瞧  真是个帅小伙儿
Look at you. You're a beautiful little man.
我要给你一个见面吻
I'm going to kiss you hello.
我能亲你吗
May I do that?
你在这里能学到东西吗
Are you learning a lot here?
奶奶真替你开心
That makes Mima so happy
因为我想让你变得聪明
because she wants you to be smart.
想让你变成聪明绝顶的人
She wants you to be the smartest boy there ever was.
我有些事情得告诉你
Now, there's something I have to tell you.
我遇见了一个男人
I met a man.
很好的男人
A very sweet man.
他叫罗伊
His name is Roy.
你肯定会喜欢他的
I think you're going to like him.
我们会生活在一起
We're all going to be together
我们会开开心心的
and that's going to make us so happy.
那样好吗
Won't that be nice?
好啦  好啦
All right. All right.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
这个
It's-- here it is.
叫"阿巴真棒"
It's an Abba-Zaba.
我也不知道这是什么
I don't know what that is,
不过肯定很好看
but I'm sure it's wonderful.
这是给你的
And it's for you.
现在我们回家吧
And we're going home now.
家里都收拾好了
It's all been taken care of.
你和我一起
You're going to come home with--
回家
with me.
你好  茱莉亚
Hello, Julia.
你好吗
How are you?
我很好
I'm very well.
他们是你的亲戚吗
Are these your relations?
他们是老师
They're teachers.
当然
Of course they are.
-那个...  -你来这里做什么
- Well, then... - What are you doing here?
带汤米回家
Just bringing Tommy home.
他不和你住在一起了
He doesn't live with you anymore.
茱莉亚  那得法官说了算
Now, Julia, that's for the judge to decide.
今天我们聊了会儿  他觉得我很有希望
We had a chat today and he was very forthcoming.
走吧  亲爱的  我在这里
Come on, sweetie. I'm here.
不不
No, no.
这样不对
This isn't proper.
今天是美好的一天  这样很不好
It's a beautiful day and this isn't proper.
我们走这边
We're going to walk this way.
好吗  而且不要回头
Okay? And we're not looking back.
-请这边走  女士  -放开我
- This way, ma'am. - Let go of me.
-我们走吧  -放开我
- Let's go. Come on. - Let go of me.
-你们没有这个权利  -请这边走
- You don't have the right. - Now, please.
你们不能把我当污点一样从他生命中抹去
You can't just bleach me out like a laundry stain.
-放开我  -快走
- Let go of me. - Come on.
我得给他"阿巴真棒"的票
I have to give him the Abba-Zaba.
就是这
Here it is.
还不错
Not bad.
还好  老妈挂的窗帘
It's okay. Ma put up the curtains.
你会弹这个
Can you play this?
不太会
Not really.
你得找个姑娘听你唱情歌
You need to find yourself a girl to serenade.
给你自己一点动力
Give you an incentive.
把门先关上  威尔
Shut the door for a minute, Will.
-努基伯父  -不说教
- Uncle Nucky-- - No lecture.
只是有些话想说
Just a few things I want to say.
不管发生了什么  都过去了
Whatever occurred, it's over.
但以后时不常  你会想起
But every now and then you'll think
这个连长什么样都记不清的男孩
about the terrible thing that happened to a boy
身上发生的惨剧
whose face you can't quite remember.
我保证  你会没事的
I promise, you can live with it.
你就是这样的吗
Is that what you do?
你会毕业
You're going to graduate.
如果有必要
We'll get you into another school
我们会帮你转学
if that's what's necessary.
现在这都不重要
It's not important now.
你担心其他人怎么说
You worry about what other people might say.
担心那些被你成为朋友的人
You worry about someone you call a friend.
这些都不重要
None of that matters.
唯一可以依赖的东西  就是血缘
The only thing you can count on is blood.
在你血管中流淌的
The blood that's in your veins
和在我血管中流淌的一样
and the blood that's in mine.
那些瞧不起你的人
The people who discount you,
他们不知道你是谁
they don't know who you are.
你感受到的愤怒  给我听仔细了
The rage you feel-- listen to me careful--
是一份馈赠
it's a gift.
用好它
Use it.
但是不要让别人看到
But don't let anyone see it.
你知道有我照管你
Know that I'm watching over you.
把你想成为的那个人展现给我
Show me the person you intend to be.
你给地方检察官多少钱
How much did you pay the district attorney?
以后我们再谈这个
One day we'll talk about all that.
现在  你就按我们之前讨论的办
Right now, you just need to stick to what we discussed
其他的事别担心
and not worry about the rest.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-你是克莱顿  -是的  先生
- You're Clayton? - Yes, sir.
你是威利的父亲
You're Willie's father?
不  是他伯父
No, his uncle.
您怎么
How do you--
我晚会再回来
I'll come back later.
-我只是  -没关系
- I was just-- - It's all right.
我得回家了
I have to get back home.
记住我说的话
Remember what we talked about.
很高兴见到你  克莱顿
It's good to meet you, Clayton.
你这一整天都去哪了
Where the hell have you been all day?
不想去上课
Didn't feel like going to class.
天呐  威尔  大家都在讨论
Christ, Will, everybody's talking about--
我们要怎么办
what are we gonna do?
都解决了
It's taken care of.
什么意思
What does that mean?
问题解决了
It's been taken care of.
他死了  威尔  你不能就这么
He's dead, Will. That's not just gonna go--
克莱顿  我得学习
Clayton, I have to study.
什么
What?
每天商学课考试
There's a test in commerce tomorrow
我得学习
and I have to study.
你让我一个人待会怎么样
So how about you leave me alone?
让我来看看你有什么本事  男子汉
Let's see what you got, tough guy.
穆勒
Mueller!
闪开  闪开
Out of the way. Move. Move.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck's going on here?
一个人数劣势的情况
A numerically disadvantaged situation.
什么
A what?
六车人在路上
There's six carloads on the way.
在人到之前别让他们出门
Just keep 'em behind that gate until they get here.
来  让我来
Come on, let me at 'em!
给你  尝尝这个
Here, take that!
没必要发生冲突  伙计们
Ain't no need for any grief, fellas.
结果早就定了
It's all sewed up anyway.
回家吧
Go home.
好好吃顿晚餐
Have a nice dinner.
明天多赚点钱
Make some more money tomorrow, huh?
我们在等警察
We're waiting for the cops.
-他们不会来了  -你怎么知道
- They ain't coming. - How do you know?
我警察局认识人
I got a buddy on the force.
你们是谁
And who are you?
我们是谁  我让你知道我们是谁
Who are we? I'll show you who the fuck we are.
冷静
别他妈教我该干什么
Don't tell me what to do.
小个子  话说的挺大啊
That's big talk, little man!
用用你的脑子
你说了算吗
现在说这个重要吗
对我来说很重要
It matters to me.
这是美国
This is America!
我们需要那些多余的人手  不然就得撤了
We need those extra men or we need to leave.
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
我给你戴上顶战冠
I'll nail you in front of a cigar stand
把你钉在雪茄架上
with a warbonnet on your scalp.
尝尝这个
Take this.
情况就是这样
This is how it is.
我们要管理西塞罗
We're running Cicero.
法律上已经成为事实
It's all done legal.
不满意的  可以站出来
Anybody don't like it, then step out here.
来啊  来啊  伙计们
Come on. Come on, guys. Come on.
就一个
Just one of you.
站出来
Step out
如果你觉得你有种的话
if you think you got the fucking balls.
干倒这群外国佬混蛋们
Get them dago sons of bitches!
带着这个回芝加哥去吧
Take that back to Chicago.
他有枪
He's got a gun!
弗兰克
Frank!
我给你打了十次电话了
I called you 10 times.
我在这了
I'm here.
我做了什么错事吗
Did I do something wrong?
不是对我
Not to me.
我发现你的时候你浑身冰冷
You were very cold when I found you.
我肯定是睡着了
I must have just fallen asleep.
你现在感觉如何
How you feeling now?
好多了
Better.
今天过的不好吗
Rough day?
还是说我不该问
Or shouldn't I ask?
你在化妆间干什么呢
What were you doing in the powder room?
帮你把这个清理干净
Cleaning this up for you.
发现它们都在地上
Found it lying on the floor.
那些  那些是
That's-- that's just--
我知道是什么
Yeah, I know what it is.
能让你舒服点吗
Does that help you?
没用了
Not anymore.
那是什么感觉
How does that make you feel?
害怕
Terrified.
我只能拒绝你了
I must repulse you.
不  谁都有弱点  我了解
No. I know about weakness.
谁都有罪孽  我也了解
And I know about sin.
但你不了解我
You don't know about me.
那就跟我讲讲
Then tell me
也许能让你好受点
if that would make any of this better.
罗伊
Roy...
我做过非常可怕的事
I have done the most awful things.
布料
Tuch.
工厂
Manufaktur.
还有织布工人
Und Konfektionsgeschaft.
卡尔施泰特
Karstadt.
均为德语，卡尔施泰特是欧洲最大的百货邮购集团，位于德国
真拗口
That's a mouthful.
我们这就叫百货商店
We just say department store.
那是什么
What is that?
我们期待已久的东西
This is something we've been waiting for.
-终于到了  -来自大洋彼岸
- Now it's arrived. - From far across the seas.
副经理[德语]
Stellvertretender Direktor.
副经理
Assistant manager.
这工作好吗
Was that a good job?
很有地位
It was a position of respect.
-不就是盯住雇员  -不让他们偷鸡摸狗
- Watch over the employees. - Make sure nobody steals.
还有很多别的职责
There were many responsibilities.
不管什么职责  都是忠诚为先
And they all depended on loyalty, didn't they?
忠诚  诚实
Loyalty and honesty.
-这两点你引以为豪  -我是努力争取
- You pride yourself on that. - I strive.
努力争取  努力争取
You strive. You strive.
你告诉过妻子吗
Did you even tell your wife?
-儿子们呢  -还是只带着钱跑了
- Your sons? - Or just leave with the money?
钱和情妇
The money and mistress.
她是卖内衣的
She worked behind the lingerie counter.
卖了多久
How long did that last?
没多久
Not long.
快乐总是不长久啊
So much for happiness, huh, Ed?
我是美国的合法公民
I am a legal resident of the United States.
我说你是什么你就是什么
You are what I say you are.
我说你不属于这
And I say you don't belong here.
那把我驱逐出境吧
Then deport me.
一站时  我在军情处
I was Army Intelligence during the war.
我觉得德语特别美妙
I thought the language was very beautiful.
前面那段德语以及下文均节选自舒伯特——《魔王》
"父亲怀抱爱子  深夜在风中飞驰
"A father rides with his son through night and wind.
孩童惊恐万分
The child is terrified.
是那林中的恶魔
A demon in the woods.
魔王"
The Elfking."
父亲说了什么  埃迪
What does the father say, Ed?
吾儿  那只是一片迷雾
Mein Sohn, es ist ein Nebelstreif.
-"只是一片迷雾"  -对
- "Only a wisp of fog." - Ja.
但父亲错了  魔王真的在那
But the father was wrong and the Elfking is real,
他儿子  用美妙的德语告诉我  他儿子怎么了
and the son-- what happens to the son, Ed, in beautiful German?
爱子  却已于怀中长眠
In seinen Armen... In seinen Armen das Kind war tot.
"爱子
"In his arms
却已于怀中长眠"
the child was dead."
你的儿子  康拉德和卢卡斯  已经成年了
Your boys, Konrad and Lucas, they're grown men now.
卢卡斯都有儿子了
Lucas has a son of his own.
-什么  -他们改姓了
- What? - They changed their last name.
当你根本不存在
As if you didn't even exist.
为了忘记他们的父亲  盗贼  骗子
To escape the shame their father the thief,
叛徒
the liar, the traitor
带给他们的耻辱
brought upon them.
再过六天
Six days from now,
我们就把你移交给汉诺威警局
you'll be in the custody of the Hanover police.
让你的儿子们重新认识一下你
Then you and your boys will get acquainted all over again.
他们肯定特别开心
Think how glad they'll be to see you.
你想要什么
What do you want from me?
要你嘴里的信息
We want you to tell us something.
什么  要什么
What? What?
我不知道
I do not know.
你要我说什么
What do you want me to say?
-你决定  -决定好了  就可以走了
- You decide. - You decide and you can go.
我不明白
I do not understand.
很简单  埃迪
It's very simple, Ed.
只要说一件事  一件小事
You tell us one thing, one little thing,
今天就算结束了  我保证
and we're done for today. You have my word.
就当是表一下忠心
Call it a demonstration of loyalty.
拉尔夫·卡彭
Ralph Capone.
然后呢
Yes?
在火车站
At the train station.
我把钱给了他
That was the man I gave the money to.
为什么
Why?
因为
Because...
努基要我那么做
that is what Nucky told me to do.
你看这多简单
See how easy that was?
埃迪
Ed...
回头见了
we'll see you again soon.
我刚下火车
I get off a train...
结果
and right there
就在报纸上看到
in a newspaper...
布鲁克林多好啊
What was wrong with Brooklyn, huh?
我们仨那会特别开心
We was all happy there.
阿尔说"出来吧"  我们就
Al says, "Come out," And...
他想单独和你谈谈
He wants to speak to you personal.
去吧
Go on.
没什么线索
There's not much more to go on.
据说是芝加哥警局的特警
Word has it that it was Chicago's Detectives' Special Squad.
他们说有人打电话来
They say someone called and told them
说不能相信西塞罗警局
the Cicero Police couldn't be trusted.
他枪都没掏出来
He never got his gun out.
那群王八蛋们
Every fucking thing that crawls
都他妈要付出代价
is gonna pay.
克莱顿·戴维斯
Clayton Davies?
我们是费城警局的
We're with the Philadelphia Police.
你不该来这
You're not supposed to be up here.
那就别让人看见我
Then you better not let anyone see me.
你知道发生什么了吗
Do you know what happened?
克莱顿被捕了
They arrested Clayton.
什么意思
What do you mean?
警察来了  把他抓走了
The police came and they arrested him.
说他给亨利下毒
They said he poisoned Henry.
为什么要给他下毒
Why would somebody do something like that?
你是怎么回事
The hell happened to you?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你好像在长凳上过的夜
You look like you slept on a bench.
我跟老朋友在一起
I spent the night with old friends.
喝了很多酒  非常多
There was much drinking. Too much.
不知不觉天就亮了
And the night became morning.
你要是想消失一整天
If you're going to disappear for an entire day--
不会有下次了
It will not happen again.
你这份工作是不该让我操心的  明白吗
I shouldn't have to worry about that. You understand?
我只说这么多
That's all I'm saying.
这份工作是你主动要求的
It's a responsibility that you asked for.
-你吃了吗  -不饿
- Have you eaten? - I am not hungry.
随你便吧
Suit yourself.
等等
Hold on.
过来
Come over here.
看到没
Well?
要是你在身边  就没这么麻烦了
Here's something else I'd rather not worry about.
本集中所引用的《魔王》为舒伯特根据民间传说改编创作
讲述了父亲怀抱儿子赶夜路，儿子察觉到魔鬼的存在
父亲未当真，好言好语安抚儿子
结果回到家中发现儿子已离开人世